Guide to the Arthur Levitt, Jr. Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XIII: SEC Correspondents Index
  - Weitz, Carlos E. Comision National de Valores, Argentina, TO: Oct. 19, 2000
  - Welch, John F. General Electric Company, FROM: Mar. 14, 2000; TO: Mar. 29, 2000; Oct. 4, 2000; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Wells, Frank G. Walt Disney Co. FROM: Jul. 26, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Wells, Jeffrey State Senate, CO; Council of State Governments. FROM: Mar. 18, 1997; TO: Mar. 26, 1997
  - Wellstone, Paul US Senate, FROM: Jun. 25, 1998 (RE: Jones, B. Todd); TO: Jun. 2, 1998
  - Wendt, Gary C. General Electric Capital Corporation, FROM: May 5, 1998; TO: May 28, 1998
  - Wertheim, Andrew J. US SEC - Northeast Regional Office, TO: Feb. 24, 1995
  - Werts, Jonathan Pacific Exchange Specialist Association, FROM: Jun. 10, 1998; TO: Jun. 30, 1998
  - Wessel, Richard P. US SEC - Atlanta District Office, TO: Dec. 30, 1996; May 14, 1998
  - West, Fowler North American Securities Administrators Association, Inc. TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - West, Steven K. Sullivan & Cromwell, FROM: Sep. 8, 1995; TO: Sep. 19, 1995
  - Weston, Josh S. Automatic Data Processing, Inc. FROM: Aug. 24, 1998 (RE: Trachtenberg, Steve); TO: Aug. 31, 1998; Sep. 14, 1998
  - Wetlaufer, Eric M. Boston Security Analysts Society, Inc. FROM: Dec. 12 1997; TO: Jan. 8, 1998
  - Wheat, Allen D. Credit Suisse First Boston Corp. TO: Mar. 27, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Apr. 10, 1997; Aug. 15, 1997; Oct. 17, 1997; Apr. 8, 1998; Oct. 22, 1998; Dec. 28, 1998; Jan. 5, 1999
  - Wheeler, James E. University of Michigan, MI - Business School, FROM: Oct. 22, 1998; TO: Nov. 20, 1998
  - White, John Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government, TO: Aug. 16, 1999
  - White, Mary Jo US Attorney, TO: Oct. 14, 1997
  - White, Rick US House of Representatives, TO: Feb. 18, 1997; Mar. 5, 1997
  - Whitehead, John C. AEA Investors, Inc. TO: Sep. 29, 1995; Sep. 28, 1999; Nov. 27, 2000; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Whittaker, Andrew Securities and Investments Board, UK, TO: Mar. 6, 1995 (re: Shepheard-Walwyn, Tim)
  - Wick, Charles Z. Charles Z. Wich & Associates, FROM: Sep. 22, 1995; TO: Oct. 10, 1995
  - Wigmore, Barrie A. Goldman Sachs Group, FROM: Feb. 22, 1999; TO: Mar. 11, 1999
  - Wild, Stephen K. Securities America, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Wickers, Gail PaineWebber, TO: May 2, 1995
  - Wienner, Daniel P. Adviser Investment Management, FROM: Mar. 29, 1999; TO: Apr. 5, 1999
  - Wiese, C. F. Registrar of Banks, Republic of South Africa, TO: Mar. 7, 1995
  - Wiley, David W., III Wiley Brothers Inc. TO: Aug. 23, 1995
  - Wilks, Donald R. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Williams, Harold M. J. Paul Getty Trust; Getty Foundation, FROM: May 22, 1997; TO: Oct. 5, 1995; Nov. 5, 1996; Nov. 6, 1996; Jun. 18, 1997; Jul. 28, 2000
  - Williams, Kaye Securities Industry Association, TO: Sep. 13, 1995
  - Williams, Linda New York Stock Exchange, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Williams, William J., Jr. Sullivan & Cromwell, FROM: Jan. 23, 1997; Jun. 20, 1997; TO: Jul. 7, 1995; Oct. 23, 1995; Mar. 6, 1996; Feb. 4, 1997; May 27, 1997(Balamaci, N.); Jul. 24, 1997; Feb. 27, 1998
  - Willig, Robin National Academy Foundation, TO: Apr. 14, 1998
  - Wilmers, Robert G. M&T Bank, TO: Jul. 13, 2000
  - Wilpon, Fred, FROM: May 8, 1998; TO: May 13, 1998
  - Wilson, Charles US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Wilson, Craig D. US SEC, TO: May 7, 1996
  - Wilson, Gwen DLS Group, Inc. TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Wilson, Heather US House of Representatives, TO: Dec. 22, 1999
  - [Wilson, Malcolm] Kent, Hazzard, Jaeger, Greer, Wilson & Fay, FROM: Mar. 17, 1994 (personal file)
  - Wilson, Michael RRC Dominion Securities, TO: Aug. 16, 1999
  - Wine, John, Jr. Securities Commissioner, KS, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Winkler, Matthew Bloomberg Business News, TO: Aug. 16, 1995
  - Winslow, Paul H. Apple Computer, Inc. FROM: Oct. 19, 1998; TO: Oct. 26, 1998
  - Winters, Robert Prudential Insurance Company of America, TO: Mar. 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995
  - Wisner, Frank G. US Ambassador, India, FROM: Apr. 23, 1996; TO: May 9, 1996
  - Wittich, Georg Federal Securities Supervisory Office, Germany, FROM: Apr. 29, 1997; TO: Dec. 26, 1996; Apr. 25, 1997; May 8, 1997; Nov. 19, 1998
  - Woiski, Ronny Swedish Financial Supervisory Authority, Sweden, TO: Dec. 26, 1996
  - Wolcott, Laurens E. Salisbury School, CT, TO: Jan. 2, 1996
  - Wolf, Frank R. US House of Representatives, FROM: Jan. 9, 1995 (Kathryn Fulton); Sep. 30, 1999; Oct. 7, 1999; Mar. 22, 2000; TO: Jan. 30, 1995 (Kathryn Fulton); Oct. 22, 1999; May 8, 2000
  - Wolfensohn, James D. World Bank, TO: Dec. 6, 1995; Oct. 28, 1998; Nov. 22, 1999 (RE: Maco, Paul)
  - Woods, Robert A. Woods Capital Corporation, FROM: Jun. 24, 1996
  - Woolf, Harry Institute for Advanced Study, FROM: Apr. 7, 1998; TO: Apr. 15, 1998
  - Woolsey, Lynn US House of Representatives, FROM: Dec. 10, 1997; TO: Jan. 20, 1998
  - Wouters, Joyce B. FROM: Aug. 24, 1993: TO: Sep. 13, 1993
  - Wright, Barbara R. Heather Investments, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Wright-Samuel, Rosetta US SEC - Procurement, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Wright, Jacquelyn H. US SEC - Desktop Publishing, TO: Oct. 6, 1997
  - Wright, Michael W. Supervalu, Inc. FROM: Mar. 6, 1997; TO: Mar. 13, 1997
  - Wrighton, Peter De Oude Kelder Fram, Republic of South Africa, FROM: Mar. 6, 1995TO: Mar. 7, 1995
  - Wulff, Richard US SEC, TO: Jun. 19, 1995
  - Wyden, Ron US House of Representatives; US Senate, FROM: Apr. 12, 1995; Jun. 12, 1995; Jan. 10, 1997; Feb. 13, 1998; TO: May 24, 1995; Jan. 31, 1997; Mar. 4, 1998
  - Wynn, Albert E. US House of Representatives, TO: Feb. 18, 1997; Mar. 5, 1997
  - Yagui Tomona, Alberto Comision Nacional Supervisora de Empresas y Valores, Peru, TO: Apr. 10, 1996
  - Yamaguchi, Mitsuhido Tokyo Stock Exchange, Japan, TO: Jun. 20, 1995
  - Yamashita, Russel H. Commissioner of Securities, HI, TO: Apr. 21, 1995; Jan. 5, 1998
  - Yarur Elsaca, Daniel Seperintendencia de Valores y Securos, Chile, FROM: Dec. 26, 1994; Aug. 23, 1995; Jan. 14, 1997; TO: Feb. 8, 1995; Sep. 12, 1995; Jan. 31, 1997; Jun. 25, 1999; [Nov.]. 1999; Mar. 21, 2000
  - Yormak, Jonathon Kent, TO: Sep. 27, 1995
  - Young, Bruce J. Mesirow Financial, Inc. TO: Sep. 13, 1995
  - Young, C.W. Bill US House of Representatives, TO: Aug. 22, 2000; Sep. 15, 2000
  - Young-Spitzer, Diane Securities Division, MA, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Zang, Leonard J. Customized Portfolios Ltd. TO: Mar. 20, 1996
  - Zantman, Jan Securities Board of Netherlands, TO: Dec. 26, 1996
  - Zarb, Frank National Association of Securities Dealers, FROM: Mar. 27, 1997; Aug. 7, 1997; Mar. 6, 2000; TO: Mar. 14, 1997; Apr. 4, 1997; Jul. 17, 1997 (RE: O'Neil, Roderick); Aug. 9, 1997; Aug. 25, 1997; Sep. 9, 1997; Oct. 23, 1997; Apr. 17, 1998 (2); Feb. 22, 1999; Mar. 24, 1999; Jul. 26, 1999; Mar. 8, 2000
  - Zarella, Dominic A. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Zelinka, Robert Southeast Research Partners, Inc. FROM: Nov. 6, 1995; TO: Aug. 5, 1993; Nov. 14, 1995
  - Zarr, Gary American Museum of Natural History, FROM: Aug. 2, 2000; TO: Aug. 9, 2000
  - Zehner, Mark US SEC - Office of Municipal Securities, TO: Dec. 29, 1998
  - Zeller, Wilhelm Hannover Ruckversicherungs-Aktiengesellschaft, TO: Apr. 25, 1997
  - Zhou, Xiaochuan China Securities Regulatory Commission, People's Republic of China, TO: Jan. 24, 2001
  - Zhou, Zhengqing China Securities Regulatory Commission, People's Republic of China, TO: Sep. 26, 1997; Dec. 5, 1997
  - Zimmer, Lynn, TO: Oct. 29, 1993
  - Zises, Alvin, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Zises, Helen, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Zumwalt, E.R., Jr. Admiral, US Navy (retired), FROM: Apr. 9, 1998; TO: Apr. 15, 1998
  - Zumwalt, James G., II, FROM: Nov. 21, 1995; Jun. 18, 1997; TO: Dec. 7, 1995; Jun. 27, 1997
  - Board Members Qualifications Review Board, TO: May 6, 1996
  - Board of Management Frankfurter Wertpapierborse, Germany, TO: May 28, 1996
  - Board of Directors 173-175 Riverside Drive Tenants Corp. TO: Jun. 18, 1996 (re: Carter, Jon)
  - To Whom it May Concern Downtown Sam, TO: Feb. 9, 2000 (RE: Hastings, Larry)